Hey, what
are you doing?
Jesus.
Did you get
a good look?
Blue Toyota Camry,
that's all I saw.
It's the Wartons' dog.
Oh, man.
It's not gonna make it.
Go see if they're home.
It's okay.
There are two
kinds of pain.
The sort of pain
that makes you strong
or useless pain,
the sort of pain
that's only suffering.
I have no patience
for useless things.
Moments like
this require someone
who will act.
Who will do
the unpleasant thing,
the necessary thing.
There.
No more pain.
It was
a hit and run.
I'm awfully sorry.
He must've jumped
over the fence again.
Look, Steve is gonna
file a report on the car.
He'll put his people on it.
We'll track them down.
Stunning.
Shall we?
...three, two, one.
Happy New Year!
Oh.
President-elect
Garrett Walker.
Do I like him? No.
Do I believe in him?
That's beside the point.
Any politician that
gets 70 million votes
has tapped into
something larger
than himself,
larger than even me,
as much as I hate to admit it.
Look at that winning smile,
those trusting eyes.
I latched onto him early on
and made myself vital.
After 22 years in Congress,
I can smell which way
the wind is blowing.
Jim Matthews, his Right
Honorable Vice President.
Former governor
of Pennsylvania.
He did his duty in
delivering the Keystone
State, bless his heart.
Now they're about to
put him out to pasture.
But he looks
happy enough,
doesn't he?
For some, it's simply
the size of the chair.
Linda Vasquez,
Walker's chief of staff.
I got her hired.
She's a woman, check.
And a Latina, check.
But more important than that,
she's as tough as
a two-dollar steak.
Check, check, check.
When it comes to
the White House,
you not
only need the keys
in your back-pocket,
you need the gatekeeper.
As for me,
I'm just the lowly
House Majority Whip.
I keep things
moving in a Congress
choked by
pettiness and lassitude.
My job is to clear the pipes
and keep the sludge moving.
But I won't have to be
a plumber much longer.
I've done my time.
I've backed the right man.
Give and take.
Welcome to Washington.
You need a haircut.
You think?
A little trim.
What are you
going to wear?
You mean for
the meeting?
For the announcement.
I'll wear my navy blue,
the one with the pinstripes.
Good. You look
handsome in that suit.
I don't know if
they'll announce
before your board meeting.
As long as I can say
the donation is coming.
Soon as it's official,
SanCorp will
write you a check.
This is going to be
a big year for us.
They're gonna want
to start with something big.
That's why I'm here
Really? What?
I'd say immigration,
banking or education.
But none of my regular
sources can confirm that.
Because they don't
know, or because
they're not talking?
Because they don't know.
Keep at it.
Get me something.
Sorry. Sorry,
Mr. Hammerschmidt. Zoe.
Barnes.
Right.
Did it take him a year
to remember your name?
Longer.
Good morning, Lucas.
What can I do
for you, Zoe?
I am sick of
the Fairfax
County Council.
You tell me every day.
Move me online.
My own blog.
First person.
Subjective. 500 words.
Not gonna happen.
I'll go underground.
Back rooms, the urinals.
I'll win over staff
members on the Hill.
They need
a place to vent.
A gossip column.
No. We lift the veil.
What's really going on.
This is
The Washington Herald,
Zoe, it's not TMZ.
Do you know how
many people watch TMZ?
I couldn't care less.
Which is why print
journalism is dying.
Then it'll die with
dignity. At least
at this paper.
You're stuck in
the 20th century, Lucas.
You lack imagination.
Maybe so, but right
now, I don't need
imagination, I need copy.
Your nights and
weekends are yours.
I applaud whatever
you want to do,
as long as it's
not on my time.
You're telling me
to get back to work.
I am.
What you're
really telling me
is to fuck off.
I'm telling you both.
It's Mr. Chapman, already,
from Province Trust.
Hold my calls, Christina.
Henry.
It's good to see you.
How long are you
in town for?
Just today.
You gotta come
back down for
the inauguration.
I can hook you up.
How about you hook me up
with the zoning laws
you promised to get changed?
We've got 12 million
sitting in escrow
for an empty lot
we can't build on.
I know. But you
gotta understand, it's
a local municipal issue.
I can't just
pick up the phone...
You can't?
Because that's not
what you led us to believe
when you begged for
50 grand in donations.
Right.
One sec.
Christina, I said no
calls. Not while I'm
meeting with Mr. Chapman.
The President-elect?
Do you mind?
No, go ahead, please.
Put him through,
Christina.
Mr. President-elect.
Thank you. Yes, we were...
We were pleased to
win by double digits.
Absolutely,
anything you need.
I need you to
put your long, wet,
talented tongue
between my thighs
and make me
squeal like Monica...
Me too, me too.
Okay. Thank you, sir.
I'm so sorry.
Where were we?
Walker, what's he like?
Is the President-elect
running late?
No. He couldn't make it.
I'll brief him, though.
Okay.
This is the memo I drafted
on our Middle East policy
we've been developing.
Now, I wanna borrow
from Reagan,
I'd like to coin the phrase
"trickle-down diplomacy."
That way...
Frank, I'm going
to stop you there.
We're not nominating you
for Secretary of State.
I know he made
you a promise, but
circumstances have changed.
The nature of
promises, Linda,
is that they remain immune
to changing circumstances.
Garrett has thought long
and hard about this,
and he's decided we need
you to stay in Congress.
When was this
decision made?
And why wasn't I
part of a conversation?
I'm sorry, Frank.
If it had been up to me,
I wouldn't have waited
this long to tell you.
So you knew you
were going to do this.
It has been
an evolving discussion.
It's a chicken-shit move.
Frank...
I was vetted.
Was that a ruse?
No.
Let's be absolutely clear.
You wouldn't
have won without me.
You're right.
But now we have to lead,
and that means
making tough choices.
As you know,
education is
a top priority for us.
A complete
federal overhaul.
But it's not just
education, Frank.
Congress is split.
We need you there
more than we need you
in the State Department.
I got you
hired, Linda.
I know.
Donations, endorsements.
I wrote the campaign's
entire foreign
policy platform.
I bring years
of foreign affairs
committee...
Frank, please.
I wanna speak to
Walker personally.
The decision is made.
We need you, Frank.
Will you stand
beside us or not?
Of course. If that's
what the President wants.
I'm very glad
to hear that.
I'm curious.
If not me, then who?
Michael Kern.
Well, that is
an excellent choice.
Can we make
it more clear?
I just want to make
sure it doesn't look like
we're neglecting
our domestic...
No. No, no, no.
I'm gonna say that we're
expanding our mission.
Okay.
And we're bringing
on a new organization
to help us.
Do you know
which one yet?
I'm still looking into
a few options, but...
Tell me, what did we agree
on, that we could hire
how many new people?
Six?
Six, maybe seven.
We'll have enough.
It's exciting.
This new direction
we're heading.
I just don't know
where we're going to fit
all the people.
Do you think we
have to look into
additional space?
No, no, no, no.
I'll find a way.
Okay, so make the changes
to the PowerPoint
and let's meet
again at 2:30.
Okay.
It's me.
I feel like
an idiot leaving
messages like this.
Call me back.
What is it, Zoe?
Um...
I know you're going
to have your hands full
at the White House,
so if you need
someone to do research
or punch out background...
I think I'll be fine.
Well, if things
get hectic, and
you need any help.
So you can blog
about rubbing shoulders
with the big boys?
What did Lucas tell you?
Look, no offense,
Zoe, but I don't have time
to be anyone's
training wheels.
I just thought...
No, I was actually
offering to lend a hand.
That's it.
Got it. Thanks.
Claire...
You didn't call.
I was...
You didn't call
me, Francis.
Nine hours.
You don't not call me.
Not when it's this big.
You're right.
When have we ever
avoided each other?
I wanted
a solution first.
Do you have one?
Not yet.
This affects me
too, Francis.
And it's not the money
I'm upset about.
It's that we do
things together.
When you don't involve me,
we're in free fall.
I should have
called you
and I didn't.
What happened?
She says they need to
keep me in Congress.
Linda said that?
Walker wasn't even there.
That's what
really gets me.
He didn't have
the courage to
look me in the eye...
I knew you shouldn't
trust that woman.
I didn't. I don't.
I don't trust anyone.
Then how could you
not see this coming?
I never thought
they were capable.
You don't usually
underestimate people,
Francis.
I know.
Hubris. Ambition.
You should be angry.
I'm livid.
Then where is that?
I don't see it.
What do you
want me to do?
Scream and yell?
Throw a tantrum?
I want more than I'm
seeing. You're better
than this, Francis.
Well, I'm sorry,
Claire.
I am sorry.
No. That I won't accept.
What?
Apologies.
My husband doesn't
apologize, even to me.
How long have
you been up?
Hours.
I know what
I have to do.
Good.
We'll have a lot
of nights like this,
making plans,
very little sleep.
I expected that.
That doesn't worry me.
I better get to work.
I laid a suit out
for you upstairs.
The navy blue one.
I love that woman.
I love her more
than sharks love blood.
Why do you think
they went with him?
We're too good.
They can't afford to
lose us in Congress.
He's had work done.
A chin tuck probably.
He definitely dyes his hair.
Do we say anything?
No. God, no.
Not unless he brings it up.
Nancy?
9:25...
Cancel everything.
Stamper, you're with me.
Now, look...
They've done us
a great favor, Doug.
We are no longer
bound by allegiances.
We serve no one.
We live by one rule
and one rule only,
never again will we
allow ourselves to be
put in such a position.
Walker and Vasquez.
All of them.
I hold them
all accountable.
Retribution?
No.
No. It's more than that.
Take a step back.
Look at
the bigger picture.
I think I see what
you're getting at.
Kern first?
That's how you
devour a whale, Doug.
One bite at a time.
Who would you want?
For Secretary of State?
Give me a list of choices.
And however we do this,
we'll also need a buffer.
You mean an errand boy?
Yes.
Somebody we
control completely.
I'll keep my
ear to the ground.
Good.
I haven't eaten
since yesterday.
I almost pity him.
He didn't choose to
be put on my platter.
When I carve him up
and toss him to the dogs,
only then will he
confront that brutal,
inescapable truth.
"My God, all I ever
amounted to was chitlins."
"And he that
shall humble himself
shall be exalted."
Matthew 23:12.
Thanks be to God.
I'd like to speak today
on the subject of humility.
A lot of you have
just won re-election.
If you hadn't,
you might not
be sitting here.
And of course,
we should enjoy our success,
and be grateful for it.
But never let your
gratitude sour into pride.
You'll have many
challenges ahead over
the next couple of years.
And a person's character
isn't determined
by how he or she
enjoys victory,
but rather how he
or she endures defeat.
Nothing can help
us endure dark times
better than our faith.
Claire.
Hello, Felicity.
How are you?
Good. How are you?
Good. I'm sorry about that.
It's just not right.
Charles and I can't
understand what
Walker was thinking.
That's very sweet
of you, but really,
between you and me,
I think Francis
is relieved.
He just feels
much more at home
in Congress.
I would've bet
a million dollars
they were going to pick you.
Well, it's a good thing
you have a million
dollars to spare.
But you are by far
and away the only choice.
I appreciate you
saying that.
I mean, Michael?
Come on.
He's got half
the experience you do...
Garrett is a smart man.
He knows what he's doing.
You're a bigger man
than I, Frank.
You want some
of that wine?
Yes, definitely.
Man, this is some good shit.
Where did you get it?
I kind of lifted
it from the VIP room
of the Speakers'
holiday party.
I'm impressed.
Bordeaux, 20 years old.
It seemed about
right for you.
Ouch.
Why would you
say that to me?
I'm almost 30.
That's practically
ancient in your book.
I don't discriminate
when it comes to age.
Really?
When's the last
time you hired
a 40-year-old staffer?
Doesn't mean I wouldn't.
As long as she's
good in the sack.
Come on.
Well, it's true,
isn't it?
Where's this coming from?
You're not gonna
just toss me aside
for some slut
straight out of Vassar?
So we're having
that conversation.
It's been six months.
It's not a little
office fling anymore.
You want me to say
those three magic words.
One of which
starts with an L.
Okay, I'll say 'em.
Christina Gallagher,
lick my balls.
Oh, my...
You're a bastard.
I love you.
I love you, Christina.
Now will you
lick my balls?
So I'm curious.
Are we patrons,
benefactors or lepers?
Believe it or not,
we're angels.
I'm gonna go outside
and pretend to
use my cell phone.
Go.
Oh!
Can I have your jacket?
Yeah.
Okay.
Are you coming to bed?
I'll be up in a bit.
Don't stay up all night.
No, I'll be right there.
Thanks so much.
I'll call you.
Wait. I thought
you had a good time.
I did. I loved it.
I've never been before.
Well, maybe
I could come up.
Oh.
Brian, you're
so sweet. Really.
But if I was going to
fuck you, you'd know.
Thanks so much.
She's here.
Send her in.
It's quite rare for
a president's chief of staff
to climb the Hill.
A gesture of respect,
no doubt, or desperation.
I'm guessing she'll say
Donald Blythe for Education.
Let's see if I'm right.
Good morning, Linda.
Thank you so much
for making the trip up.
Of course. My pleasure.
Education?
First things first.
The seating chart
for the inauguration.
How do these two
work for you and Claire?
Wow.
They come with
a complimentary set
of tickets to
the Jefferson Ball.
Claire will be
over the moon.
Good, I'm so glad.
So, education.
We have Donald Blythe
drafting the legislation.
Donald Blythe? Jesus.
I know.
So you want a bill
just two steps
left of Karl Marx?
I advised the
President-elect
against it,
but Donald is
the face of education.
He's been pushing
reform for 25 years.
You want me to
guide him to the middle.
We need a bill
we can pass.
Do I have absolute autonomy
and authority on this?
There's more.
Garrett wants
the bill on the floor
in the first 100 days.
He wants to make a pledge
in his inaugural address.
That's...
That's very ambitious,
Linda.
Can we make that pledge?
A hundred days?
I can deliver.
Keep me posted.
I'll talk with Donald.
I'll check in with
you later in the week.
Terrific.
Did you smell that?
The smugness?
The false deference?
She thinks I can be
bought with a pair
of tickets. What am I?
A whore
in post-war Berlin
salivating
over free stockings
and chocolate?
What she's asking will
cost far more than that.
Ferguson?
Too old.
Willis?
Too stupid.
Boyd?
Too queer.
Really?
He's married
with three kids.
And wouldn't
they be devastated.
All right.
What about
Catherine Durant?
Cathy Durant.
She was vocally
anti-Walker.
She's got the experience.
Set up a meeting.
Hey.
The donation
from SanCorp?
The money will
have to come from
somewhere else.
What happened?
I've looked over
the budget for fiscal '13
and we've allocated
$1.6 million for salaries.
We need to
cut that in half.
You're suggesting...
Evelyn, we're going
to let some people go.
That would be
half of our staff.
We have to
carve out some room.
You would have to fire
some essential people
who have been with us
since the beginning.
We are a charity,
but not for our employees.
You know, Claire,
I've held my tongue about
this whole international
thing for a while,
but I don't get it.
We are really good
at what we do.
Why do we have to try
and be something we're not?
Because we've
plateaued, Evelyn.
And it is time
for us, for our entire
organization...
But digging wells in Africa?
We don't know
anything about that.
Which is why
we have to
bring in new people.
This is the plan
that I've proposed
to the board
and we are moving
forward with it.
I'd like a list
of names, please.
Claire, can we just
think about this?
I have thought about it.
I've put a lot of
thought into it.
But I think...
Evelyn, you're
the office manager.
I need you to trust that
I know what I'm doing.
So please get me that list
as soon as possible.
Ma'am. You can't go up.
I'm sorry.
I just have
one question.
No. No.
Sir, I apologize,
this woman...
Congressman.
Miss, you need to
step away from the door.
If I could just
have one second.
Step away from the...
Who are you?
My name is Zoe Barnes.
I'm a reporter at
the Washington Herald.
It is after
10:30 at night
and this is my home.
I do not allow...
We're part of a mutual
admiration society.
You're a fan
of the symphony.
More for the
people-watching
than the music.
It's all right, Steve.
Come on in, Ms. Barnes.
It's strong.
You'd prefer it weak?
No, the stronger
the better.
There's no harm
in looking.
That's a cheap ploy.
It's cheap but effective.
Well, you certainly have
my undivided attention.
Good,
the reason I'm here...
Oh...
Is foreplay over?
I read somewhere
that JFK never lasted
more than three minutes.
The point being?
Time is precious.
Powerful people don't have
the luxury of foreplay.
Okay. So why are
you here, Ms. Barnes?
I need somebody
I can talk to.
We're talking.
Tell me what
we're talking about.
I protect your identity,
I print whatever you tell me.
And I'll never
ask any questions.
And what makes you think
I don't already have
such an arrangement
with one of
your colleagues?
Because if you did,
you wouldn't have
let me through the door.
I've led a very long,
very successful career
avoiding this sort of
intrigue with the press.
I can't see any
advantage in starting now.
But is there
any disadvantage?
Sloppiness, for one.
I promise you
absolute discretion.
So we're talking
about trust.
Use whatever word you like.
Words matter very
much, Ms. Barnes.
You should care
more about them,
given your profession.
Then yes, your trust.
So which Zoe Barnes
am I to trust?
The one who wrote
about the fireman
that married the meter maid?
Or the one who
authored a very
fine article
on a new jogging path
in Rock Creek Park.
Don't be flattered.
I read everything.
I'm better than what
they have me doing.
You know what
that feels like.
Do I?
You would have made
a great Secretary of State.
How exactly may I
help you, Ms. Barnes?
You must know
the administration's
legislative agenda.
What's coming up first.
I may.
Will you tell me?
What would be your guess?
Education.
Why?
Immigration is
too controversial.
Tax-reform isn't sexy enough.
Everyone can get
behind children.
Is it education?
You might very
well think that.
I couldn't possibly comment.
A hint.
It's late, Ms. Barnes.
Can we talk again?
I hope you'll understand
that I want to
sleep on all this.
I never make
such big decisions
so long after sunset
and so far from dawn.
My cell phone's
on the back.
Did you put Ms. Barnes
in the visitors' ledger?
Not yet.
Don't.
Needless to say.
Needless.
Hello.
Claire, this is
Ms. Zoe Barnes,
of the Washington Herald.
She was just leaving.
Very nice to meet you,
Mrs. Underwood.
Drive safe.
There's a lot of ice
on the road.
I will. Thank you.
Does that work
on anybody?
Does what?
The push-up bra
and the V-neck tee?
Well, if it does,
I don't know who they are.
Okay. Relax, relax.
License
and registration.
The glove compartment,
sweetheart.
This isn't your
driver's license.
It's a Starbucks card.
Oh, shit. Sorry.
Sir, have you
been drinking?
No, I never drink
coffee at this hour.
I'm going to need you
to step out of the car.
If I was speeding,
you can write me a ticket...
Sir, step out of
the car right now.
Look, I don't want to
be a prick, but I'm
a member of Congress.
I don't care if you're
the King of China.
China doesn't
have a king.
It's a communist
ogliwarchy...
Let's go. Out.
You too, sweetie.
Fuck, that is
hard to say.
Hello?
Good. Well,
let's get him out.
Mind if I join you?
What the fuck
is going on?
I thought I was meeting...
No. You're meeting me.
It's 4:00 in
the goddamn morning.
I've got a city
council meeting in...
You've been police
commissioner for what,
almost a decade now?
We're here to
talk about my resume?
Mayor of D.C. would
look good on that
resume, wouldn't it?
We know that you've
been angling to run
for some time.
Experience is
your strong suit.
Endorsement and
fundraising are not.
We can help with that.
Russo, you're
free to go.
It was just
a few drinks.
It was enough
to get pulled over.
I wasn't drunk-drunk.
Were you alone?
Yes.
Say it to my face.
Watch the road.
Say it to my face!
Yes, I was alone!
You cannot keep
doing this, Peter.
It's going to
catch up with you.
I know.
Do you think we
can arrange two more
at our table for
the Jefferson Ball?
For whom?
The Holburns.
Why on earth would
you want them there?
I'm going to need
her money for the CWI.
The staff cuts
are just not enough.
I'll talk to Vasquez.
How're we doing?
Good.
Progress.
Irons in the fire.
I like irons.
But I love fire.
Yes...
What are you...
The bill is garbage, Donald.
Tax increases?
Ban on vouchers?
Federal oversight?
How do you expect
me to get that
through a committee?
When Linda told
me to write it,
she promised...
I'm sure she said
any number of things.
Forget what they
promised you, Donald.
They want your name
because it carries weight.
Well, my name
comes with my ideas.
I understand,
but you've got
to be reasonable.
This isn't the Great Debate.
It's about passing
meaningful reform.
Maybe not everything
you would hope.
But help me help you.
That's going
to take time.
Those ideas, I've been
developing them for...
If it's time you need,
I will buy you time.
But you've got to
promise me your next at bat
is gonna give me
something I can work with.
Okay, Frank,
I'll see what I can do.
Good. And, Donald,
don't let this get you down.
Together,
we're going to do more
than you've been
able to do in 25 years.
Two things are
now irrelevant.
Donald Blythe
and Donald Blythe's
new draft.
Eventually,
I'll have to re-write
the bill myself.
Forward, that is
the battle-cry.
Leave ideology to
the arm-chair generals.
It does me no good.
Walker just nominated Kern.
It's a long road
to confirmation.
Kern is a boy scout.
Nobody's a boy scout.
Not even Boy Scouts.
What do you have?
Absolutely nothing.
Then what are
we talking about?
Just asking a simple
question, does the
job interest you?
Why would you
want Michael gone?
Cathy, you and
I came up together.
The Foreign Affairs
Committee needs
a secretary we can work with.
Someone who isn't
afraid to stand up
to Walker when he's wrong.
We need you.
Let's assume
I am interested.
I don't want
to assume.
I want to know.
2... Okay. 2-6-3-7.
Please hold. Zoe Barnes.
Anywhere you want.
On my way. I'll gonna
have to call you back.
I'm so sorry.
I couldn't catch a cab.
I had to take a train and I...
Just before you
left my house.
Think back.
What were
we discussing?
The president's
legislative agenda.
Specifically.
Education.
Was I right?
Do the math,
Ms. Barnes.
He needs a bill.
Sponsored by?
You?
Be smarter than that.
Somebody with legitimacy.
Good.
And who screams
"legitimacy"
in Education?
Donald Blythe?
Correct.
The problem is...
He's an old-school
tax-and-spend liberal.
Walker ran as a moderate.
You think Blythe
would talk to me?
He doesn't have to.
Wait...
We're in a very gray area,
ethically, legally,
which I'm okay with...
I just love
this painting,
don't you?
We're in
the same boat now, Zoe.
Take care not to tip it
over. I can only save one
of us from drowning.
He announces
his education
initiative on Monday.
Half of the address is...
I understand.
Do we need
to take it out?
We're fine, Linda.
But you just
got through saying
he has to start over.
I didn't choose
Blythe. You did.
You put him in my lap
and asked me to work
a miracle, and I will.
Now, have a little
faith, Linda.
Let me work with
Donald on this.
I know what can
be accomplished
in 100 days.
All right, Frank,
we're counting on you.
Good.
Now, I do have
a little favor to ask.
Do you think I can get
just two more tickets
for my table at
the Jefferson Ball?
Drink?
Sure, what do you got?
Whiskey. Blends.
If you're offering.
So, how are things in
the City of Brotherly Love?
We're getting by.
Good, good.
I'm sorry, I
made that neat.
Did you want...
No, this is perfect.
So, it seems
you've been
a bit irresponsible.
What?
Don't play dumb
with me, Peter.
Save it for
the ethics committee.
Drink up, you could
use a little
courage right now.
You're not having one?
It's a bit early
in the day for me.
Is this about
the other night?
How do you
know about that?
I'm the Whip.
It's my job to know.
Look, they let me off.
There's no charges.
It's all taken care of.
Honestly, Peter,
do you really think
these things
just take care
of themselves?
You...
It was just this
one time, Frank.
I swear to God.
Then you must hold
God in very low esteem,
because we both know
that's a lie.
Solicitation,
controlled substances,
driving under
the influence...
You've got quite
a long list of hobbies.
What is it you want?
Your absolute,
unquestioning loyalty.
Always.
Do not misunderstand
what I mean by loyalty.
Anything. Name it, Frank.
You seem far
too relaxed.
I'm not.
You shouldn't be.
Doug will be in touch.
Hang on. Where
have you been?
I've been calling you.
Everybody's
working double-time
on inauguration
and you just up
and disappear...
Hang on.
Let me call you back.
Where did you get this?
Wrong question.
The right question is
how quickly can we
get it up on the site?
I have to run
this past Tom.
Let's get legal on this,
make sure we're not
breaking any laws.
You won't tell
me your source?
I can't do that.
Fine. But if legal
finds even one...
I understand.
How long do you
think that will take?
We should get this
online right away.
I'm not just
going to scan
a 300-page document
and put it up
before we've gone
through every...
I did that already.
The whole thing?
Cover to cover.
I've got excerpts. Analysis.
3,000 words ready for editing.
You start going over that.
Get graphics
working on tables, charts,
the whole nine yards.
Janine!
What's the angle,
five words?
Far left of center.
That's four.
Very far left of center.
Enough to put
Walker on his heels?
Fuck his heels.
This will put him on his ass.
What's up?
We've got a copy
of the administration's
education bill.
You're going to
work with Zoe,
do background copy.
Zoe Barnes?
Right here.
Whatever she needs.
Shouldn't I be
writing the...
She wrote it already.
And I want you to re-write
it, then re-write it again.
You'll help her.
Tom, I'm your chief
political correspondent.
Go.
I want this by tomorrow.
But I need to focus
on the inauguration.
This is more important.
Let's get started.
...that I will
faithfully execute the office
of President of
the United States.
"...that I will faithfully
execute the office..."
Power is a lot
like real estate.
It's all about location,
location, location.
The closer you
are to the source,
the higher your
property value.
Centuries from now,
when people
watch this footage,
who will they see
smiling just at
the edge of the frame?
"So help me God."
Congratulations.
Today is not about
the next four years.
It's about
the next four decades.
You've placed
your faith in me,
and I, in turn,
choose to place that
faith in our children.
Our children
are the key to
this nation's future,
and that's why
the first order of business
for this administration
will be a comprehensive
education reform bill
to properly fix, finance
and strengthen our
nation's schools.
And I pledge to you,
we will have that bill
on the floor of the Congress
within the first 100 days
of this administration.
It was so nice
of you to make this possible.
When you called
me, I was...
Not another word.
I'm going to miss
out on my ultimate
Frisbee league this season.
No, I'm serious.
A few of us on Budget
have quite a rivalry
going with
the guys on Finance.
It's fierce.
We get physical.
Anybody gets between
me and that goal line,
I will take that sucker down.
Donald, I've been looking
for you everywhere, maestro.
Yeah.
Let me help
you out there.
I really like
the work you've done
on the new draft.
It's a big step
forward. We're going to
make history together.
Thanks for your
encouragement, Francis.
Listen, I've got some
ideas about subsidies...
Catherine! Hold on to
that thought, Donald.
Don't you look stunning.
We Southern girls
clean up well
when we get out
of our Daisy Dukes
and into some Vera Wang.
And we Southern boys are
slow with our words,
but we're fast on our feet.
May I have the honor?
You most certainly may.
Morning, Freddy.
Mornin', Frank.
How's tricks?
Can't kick.
You want to go on in?
No, why don't you
set me up outside?
Outside?
It's freezing out here.
Well, a little cold
never hurt anybody.
Anything you
say, Frank.
It'll be right up.
My one guilty pleasure
is a good rack of ribs.
Even at 7:30 in the morning.
I have the whole
place to myself.
Freddy sometimes
opens up just for me.
Where I come from
in South Carolina,
people didn't have two
pennies to rub together.
A rack of ribs was
a luxury, like...
...Christmas in July.
This web traffic
is absolutely crazy.
...blue Camry's
wanted in connection
to a canine hit-and-run.
Hey, is this your car?
What's going on?
You want
seconds, Frank?
I better not.
Tell you what, Freddy.
Yes, I will.
I'm feeling hungry today.